Come to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Dance to the mystery
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So
Let the tarot move
We are Kangol
This is Lilith Scorpiana and you're watching Psyche Awakens TV.
Psyche Awakens TV is a portal to the shadows of the soul where truth burns through illusion
and transformation demands courage.
Psyche rips open the veil of the soul, dragging you into the abyss where raw truth claws at
your core and transformation devours all fear.
It's a relentless plunge into that only the brave emerge reborn.
Enjoy!
A small betrayal
A mirror's edge and the heart's parade
You drew your truth in silent lies
Symbols bleeding through the veil
Lost taste in like red berries
But if we just have to look, there's always a crack in the cold
Don't stare straight, look sideways
Oh, boony tail, wait here, it's getting along.
Isn't that like some kind of like, German thing?
I don't, I don't.
Oh, I like that.
That was a new song.
What's up, Stax?
Stax, Darryl.
Guys, look, hold on, can I show you?
Yeah, I can show you.
I mean, it's not perfect.
A vacuum.
How are we doing?
Okay.
I don't know.
There's this woman named Hannah.
I was always warned about her. Oh, she's not a nice person. She's not I felt bad for her
So I said her full things back unfortunately, I'm I can get petty too
Especially when people like there's I'm sitting right there. They're sitting saying I'm munching on fleas
Much on this bitch
I'm sorry, I shouldn't say that
Yeah
God he was right
Alexandra is right. I mean it's like
Joni's right listen to certain people you should listen to this live, okay
So, I don't know.
Dude, I hang out for a little bit. I'm sorry. I did end the stream this morning. I was trying to tell everybody
I was like, hey, can we go a little bit light on the politics, especially like the Middle East sort of stuff?
I don't want to, I don't know enough about it to like debate it, talk about it. I don't think it's
go to so
Borscht and the stream because no one was listening to me. I kept saying we'd lighten up on it like not we not not not
I gotta listen to me as sometimes guys. I'm like the post, you know
There ever was this I don't know about I
Don't like politics really. I'll talk about religion and stuff. I got
Politics I don't I don't really care for
But I was interested in like this day, I mean, they've released like some EPSTEIN stuff, right?
Which I really don't care about. I think it's all a horse
Pocky or whatever, but
It's interestingly they also released at the same time all this like JFK stuff about. Oh, well, maybe that wasn't the right
Gotta look when they're like kind of distract you from stuff, I don't know
I mean, it's interesting timing.
Okay, we're gonna go back in like 1963, really?
I mean, really?
How, if we're gonna go back 50 years
of political history, like now?
Kind of weird.
Anyway, I'm sorry if I have my washer
and dryer going on in this country.
I'm gonna have to hide it back up, back up.
You guys can say hi in the chat.
Guess I don't know. I'm gonna give away all my grievances today. Okay. I
Like my shirt
So yeah, I had a really nice conversation with a friend that really
Feel better
Okay, so basically I'll take requests. I'll take questions
I'm gonna talk about
No, wait, I'll talk about anything. I mean it's been such a war roller coaster of stuff going on
Ghost sober, you know, it's a ghost sober is gonna be a
I knew yearly tradition and you know what? Don't tell him I said so, but he's a...
Goosebark is worse than his bite. He really does have a good heart, so don't take what he says, seriously.
Ghosts is that here? I do apologize to that person too. Hey, what's up stacks? Yeah
Yeah
Ghosts is like
He's a arguer. He likes to he just likes to argue if he calls it debating. I think it's like
Fighting but
Ultimately
He's not a bad. He's not a bad guy. So I'm gonna stand up for him. Also
You know, what's this I don't know why it's like all of a sudden like people are saying, oh, oh
Psyche does not deserving. I
Whatever if you don't feel like I deserve a donation, you don't have to donate but why do you have to like?
Go after other people that
Do and as I don't know is it is like it's hurtful
Well, I
Don't know, you know, I
I'm a cat daddy. I
Want to be a great cat daddy. I have to
If I have to, you know, go beg on the side of the corner
for change for Cap, I will.
Fortunately, it's never had to come to that,
but I don't know.
It's like, I have to survive, too.
I don't understand.
Do you see how skinny I am?
It's not just from like, you know, it's nothing.
I'd like to thank God for McDonald's, guys.
We need a lot of free McDonald's lately.
Anyway, so what's going on?
I guess I'll do a collective reading.
Let me get these cards out.
This is called activation set.
These are sacred geometry patterns, I'll tell you.
They're really cool cards though.
This is a collective that means that, you know,
may resonate with you, it may not,
but if you're here, probably will.
Maybe a message, maybe a chakra
that needs to be activated or is activating something
relevant, look at the shape, see what it means to you.
Well, I don't always say it. Do I shuffle enough? I can try to shuffle more. You hear me, okay?
Kind of quiet.
Hey, everyone's asleep.
I love sacred geometry, actually. It's really good to meditate on. I love the Shri Yantra. There are some Shri Yantras in this book.
The pre-ontra is basically how many triangles is it?
I think it's 17 triangles intersecting.
It's a powerful image.
Let me see if maybe it comes up today.
We have healing going on.
This is the healing.
You see the beautiful...
beautiful green circle you see how it's all connected to how many sides of one
two three four five six okay so there's a hexagram in there hexagram is the
also the heart right so this is very heart chakra oriented number 29 nine
plus two is 11
we have a day are we on the 20th are we at the 21st set
Oh, 20th. Okay. I'm gonna do the 20th.
And it says healing. The frequency of healing supports our intrinsic ability to restore our health
and wholeness by consciously using the information that comes to us
through our senses and harmonizing everything accordingly.
And that is really like, you know, the hexagram is associated with the heart chakra.
Because it's like that as it's like the two the above and the below connecting right to take two triangles
Intersect them six sides
And the green two green is associated with healing and also
You know growth
I love the roundness in that it's wholeness, and it's all connected to okay. That's what we got. Oh
We have the crown chakra. Look at that beautiful purple card
Crown chakra
The crown chakra is actually it's even kind of out of the body it's on top of our head
It's the highest frequency. It's a beautiful violet right frequency of our crown chakra the violet flower of life
Supports our spiritual connection to the universe and our ability to transmute negative energy into light
And where do we do that? We do that through the mind
Right from the top of the skull
Also looking at look at the flower of life if you look closely at it. You can see it all connects right?
You can look at it like the top of your head, baby your crown, right?
It's a nice day of cleaning, and...
Okay.
Well, I'll probably just do like a couple more parts.
It looks like there's nobody interested in chat today.
So, I'll probably just leave.
Even though we're 15. Interesting, 15 is usually the devil card. It just says compassion.
And compassion is very important because that's actually like being able to empathize, being able to
be kind. Kindness, that's so important for me. I love kindness.
I think it's one of the most important lessons as a human being is to be kind to other people.
It's actually just being kind to yourself too.
The frequency of compassion supports our ability to stand by others without judgment
and be the divine mediator between heaven and earth, spirit and matter,
so that unconditional love can flow from source through our heart and into the world.
And so again, this is very similar to this healing card.
I think once we do heal ourselves,
we're able to heal others.
And we show higher self, which is this beautiful.
Hey, Trevor, how are you?
What's up, dude?
Yeah, I just pulled a few of these sacred geometry cards.
I pulled the healing card.
So I think...
We are definitely going through a healing process constantly. We're going through this process, but I think especially right now. I think
For me it really really hits like you know feeling hurt at times, but then
Being able to
You know get through it heal this
Crown shocker connection to the higher self the violet flame the
mediator between the heaven and the earth.
And finally, the compassion.
Most important to have compassion
for ourselves and each other.
Why do you still have your picture there?
Who are you?
Have your picture?
Where?
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Oh, Trevor took your picture.
Trevor, is there someone following you?
That your friend oh, it's you. Okay. Yeah, there's Trevor. Yeah, why do you have?
Take down my picture. So is that I?
Can't see it. Let me see
Hold on
What are you talking about?
Are you, who are you, EZ?
Trevor heads on his phone.
Trevor's not doing it.
Trevor, Trevor, is this my friend, Trevor?
Or my, like my, yeah, Trevor's a cool guy.
I don't think so.
Leave Trevor alone.
I, yes, I believe you, Trevor.
If you're the Trevor, I think you are.
You're the Trevor from Benny's
that always comes on the show, right?
My friend, okay.
Oh, okay, Smith, go ahead.
Okay, yes, my buddy.
I love Trevor.
Trevor's a good dude.
This is Christina Ricci's deck called Cat Full of Spiders.
Okay.
There's some asshole in KZ.
I don't believe he is, but even if he is Smith,
like, I'm not gonna put it on the screen.
So, this is a big deal.
I can't I can't barely make anything out. Yeah, I think here he's lying
where
Red runs in a spiritual war. We're here. Oh, yeah
Red runs
Okay, well look at this we have the chariot card chariot is forward successful movement something is going forward
Successfully as planned
You got some momentum going in something
You got the wheels something's moving you along. So there you are a
Smith I don't know who you are, okay?
And I know who he is and so
Yes, I'm gonna believe him. I don't know. It's my name Smith
Smith is like a fake name. It's not the name of like the Matrix police
Will tell him will tell him take it down
Shut up
You're not a mod you're not a member or like I've never even seen you before and when you're causing problems my chat already
Over this picture like I can't even make out a face on his picture. Yeah, he's just a troll
But anyway, we're moving past it. We're moving past it. They got this cherry card
Okay, I don't think a little bit like a stewardess a little bit or like a
There's a cute little cat there too cat power
Yeah
Thank you, Loki. Thank you, Loki. Oh look at this card. I got some cards mixed up in here. Shoot. Okay
Well, that could be significant. We have this one that says garden
This is from a different kind of death. Oh remember I just said spaceship and like there's a spaceship kind of thing, right?
This one says it's called spaceship actually. What is it? Is it mermaids?
Interesting says don't be afraid to sing
Our body is kind of like a spaceship, a vehicle.
Here are these vibrations.
Yeah, that's, my empire is crumbling,
banana eating chip, oh my gosh.
Yeah, you know, I know it's crumbling.
I only, this is, I think my second best month on YouTube.
How does that crumbling, I don't understand what you mean.
You know what's crumbling is your mind
Because you're stupid. Oh, we also the garden it says
Any mother glass though, I'm sorry, I've been going live
It says
Something lovely will grow from this, you know, even like these and look at it's really cute. You picture something
Lovely will grow from this and so even from the dirt right but what do things grow out of the dirt?
And do we go we've we all have to go through some dirt to like get you know get where we are, right?
Which is on top of the world right now, right?
Okay, so these cards are just from another deck
But they're mixed in so
I'll take them
Okay
Let's get a few more. This is a collective reading by the way
Oh, look at the stun. I love the sun card. It's usually the most positive card in the deck
We have Christina Ricci as the like the the creator of this deck, but look at she's
Got these beautiful flowers. She's got a halo. She's glowing
Trevor you're my friend Trevor
I'm gonna mod you and you can do with that person what you wish
is they're not really impressing me with their bullshit.
Nor is Banana Eating Champ.
Audio's Banana Eating Champ,
and welcome to the team show.
They get a haircut. No, I just have my hair tied it back. I have my hair tied back today. Yo, Alex. How are you my friend?
Someone's calling me. Hold on. Let me make sure it's somebody I know. Let's see. Oh
You know, I don't think it's I think it's that dick that's threatening me and
Called me the n-word and then when I said n-i-g-g-e-r. He said I was racist, right?
What else do we have we have the Hierophant? Okay, this is a connection
This is like a very Lilithy card, right? They usually have a male Hierophant, but this is because you got the owls, right and
In the kind of you know my Lilith I see you see the little gothic kind of Lilith, but also like a red head
But yeah, this one has a kind of a showgirl kind of thing and
Think that you know religion is kind of a big show right got the costumes. You like the owls. Yeah, there's pretty cool
owls there
So she got this feather kind of
kind of thing and see now
Religion which the Hierophant is kind of the connection between the the human and the divine
It is a bit of a show right
So maybe you're interested in and going down an official path or learning more about a path
What else we got? Oh, we got the Ace of Pentacles. This is like a seed, right? So he's on the record player and
Maybe like being inspired by some music and then this music will
Maybe grow into something that you know, maybe she'll start playing instrument or
Singing or something gets him my kind of idea that will make money. I don't know listens for messages of music
does have this
The pentagram right there, but it also kind of looks like the eye, right?
Hey you man, how are you?
Yeah, it's an ally and yeah, thank you so much, and we have
Ooh, we have a nine of cups, okay
This nine of cups is like a happy card. It's like it's almost the complete happiness, but there's one more thing
She wants like there's one thing and she's like you can see in her face. She's like I'm she sees it
She sees it and she's like right there at the
precipice at the
At the gateway to what she really wants and so I don't this is something it's like 10 of cups is gonna be the long-term happiness
nine of cups is gonna be
You're almost there
You're almost there and also
Protecting the happiness that you do have don't don't
In order to like just find out
That that last cup don't leave don't leave your other cuffs behind and or don't neglect them, right?
It's a pretty cool card. There's a got all these like little
Dwarves or little guys all offering her
Something yet. She's like, ah
That's some options, right? Hey summer. How are you sweetheart and?
We have the King of Cups and this is an interesting King of Cups card
King of Cups is that is you know usually kind of a masculine energy that has
reached emotional stability and
Really looks like she kind of escaped from a escape from an asylum, but
Okay, it kind of looks like she's wearing a straight jacket a little bit
So maybe she's been through some emotional stuff, but
She's perfectly happy in a normal setting too, right?
And there's another little cat right there.
The cat's like, what is the cat looking like that for?
The cat kind of has a funny look.
But, hi.
Yes, do you like a reading summer?
Absolutely, absolutely.
Let me just get these shuffle a little bit for ya.
Separate out, okay.
Hopefully you're having a great day.
Shuffle I should know. Hey everybody in chat. Yeah, I have my um, I
Have my hair tied back a little bit today, so it kind of looks a little bit
Better got my some my new glasses on
Thank you
Yeah, I had a good conversation with a friend on the phone and get a nice long chat and a laugh and
It was good
take my mind off of some of the, you know,
I have my ups and downs, you know,
but it's always good.
I have so many great people here, like you guys,
and it's like there's always somebody that cheers me up.
And so I wanna thank everybody.
And thank you all for being here today.
Okay, summer for you.
Ooh, some are wheel of fortune.
Okay, the wheel of fortune, it's like the card number 10.
Okay, and wheel of fortune in the upright
is things are going in your favor.
It's a favorable time right now.
If you wanna take maybe a risk,
there's like the little rabbit rabbits
or usually a symbol of luck, okay?
But I'd say that,
Looking at this car, there's beautiful colors in it.
Confidence, move forward confidently.
It's also the wheel of the tarot.
I think you're also fated for wonderful things, right?
But it's just a very favorable time.
Also, it's number 10, we're on the 10th month, okay?
10, and then today is the 20th, right?
So that's like two 10s, okay?
Okay, so three of cups three of cups is celebrating something with some with some friends
Usually with it with a few with two or more friends, you know
and
Maybe there's a reason to celebrate see maybe yet. There's gonna be a after this victory or this like this lucky period
Sometime to celebrate right
You know sometimes with a few people they can get complicated, right?
Third parties and so sometimes they can represent a third party situation
But I think it's more in the positive aspect of it and they are just enjoying themselves. What are they doing?
They're out running chasing running around with the cats outside, right? You got some
That's some lemonade
Nice beautiful day, right? Okay
Some celebrating for you
Okay, the world is coming through a successful,
a completion of a cycle, and also I would say,
so this is 21, tomorrow's the 21st, by the way,
but it does really remind me of this wheel
of fortune card as well.
Like you can see that they have these parallels, right?
They're kind of in the same position,
they're coming out of this circle.
I really see
Going through portals going like ascending like some kind of you know and then the celebrating to pull a couple more from this deck
And then I'll get you a sacred geometry card
Okay, well, okay, well we had the yeah, oh these stuck together. Okay
So we can we do have that the hangman so maybe you you have been feeling like I think this
I really see this as seeing something from a different perspective. Okay, I don't see it as you know
Any kind of any kind of negative thing? It was it's was stuck. It was stuck to this one and but this was in the reverse
It's a five of swords. I
Think it's like the five of swords is usually like a kind of a brutal victory. I think this is a victory that is like
Not as
it's a victory but it's not where it's like one there's one winner and then
everyone else is loser or you have to hurt anybody it's like it's like kind of
like I see like everybody winning and also you're like you're seeing things
from a different perspective you want other people to win so you it's like I
you want
You want I feel like you really want the best for people and it's like and you are seeing things different. So this is number
number the hangman is number 12 and
Five of swords is a
I just I'm glad I was in the rear I'm glad I was in the in the reverse right there, but it's also I also
Feel like
they're
It might it might be an upright a sacrifice, but I don't feel like it really feels like a sacrifice
Hold on. Okay
It's like it's like a victory. It's like a happy victory. Okay, I
Need a couple from these. Let's say here's a sacred geometry deck. Oh, this is pretty more 23
23 is a W. I'm getting a lot of winning energy right here. It says dynamic. Okay. That's a beautiful
triangle right there.
It says the frequency of dynamic and you certainly are dynamic, right?
supports our ability to harmonize between layers and aspects of different origin and frequency.
It helps us to put together a reality that is made up of many different elements,
both familiar and completely new, with ease, grace,
And a great joy. Okay. I'm seeing like also this like kind of like, you know, the evil eye symbol
I kind of have it sometimes as my thing. It kind of reminds me of that like on top of this triangle, right?
Bringing different sides together
Different colors. Let's see how beautiful a colorful it is
Okay, almost like a party hat like I'm getting celebration energy
Lot of celebration energy. Also, we got more of the circles like these portals going through okay?
Also bring being able to bring different elements together in a beautiful way
Unexpected like you wouldn't say necessarily these colors would go perfectly together, but they work somehow here, right?
I don't know. It just seems like it's a little bit festive
Colors I like that and I like the W for 23, right? Ooh, we have 42 is a tantric journey. Okay
this uh
Maybe it's some self self-love exploration or maybe with your partner, but we have a
Tantra is the ceremonial,
it can be ceremonial sex magic, right?
The frequency of tantric journey helps us to unlock
the hidden knowledge and wisdom that we intrinsically hold
about how to reach a state of wholeness and completion
through our sensual experiences with ourselves
and with another, okay, we'll look forward to that.
Finally, ooh, summer, we got the third eye chakra.
We got the beautiful, beautiful bluish, bluish violet.
And this is just being able to use that intuition you have,
see all the connections.
It's got some great psychic insights going on, right?
The frequency of the third eye shock
or the indigo flower of life supports our intuition
and our inner knowing, our imagination,
and our psychic powers.
I think that's very pretty.
You like my hair pulled back?
Thank you so much.
But look it's not in like summer more circles. It's like it's all it's all all coming together in a beautiful way for you
Okay, so I hope you like that reading summer
Where does that talk to go?
Thank you, I found like these paint like these rubber bands like they came with the wig I have so I
Think I'm supposed to tie up my hair before I put on the way next time
But um, yeah, if anyone would like some cards, I'm just doing
some readings and hanging out.
I did like, you know,
I got a little bit political earlier this morning.
And so I did like kind of end the show early.
I was trying to tell everybody I was like,
Hey, I'm not really like, you know,
I'm talking about politics that much.
I just not really, oh, no problem somewhere anytime.
Glad you liked it.
Yeah, it's a great things for you always.
Yeah.
I just say, I like to talk about the different religion
and that can be controversial.
I think politics gets a little, I just don't,
I don't really vibe with the conversations.
I can't really contribute to them that much
and then people get really upset and stuff about it.
So I'm sorry, I did end pretty early today
or kind of suddenly, but.
I said to go with my instincts there
Thank you guys, I know um the 26 viewers and four likes. Yeah, I was read I was reading some of my like
Demographics, I'm doing okay on numbers. I think I just hit like 300,000 views or something like that
But I really do have it's really sad actually when I when I look at
I can go to my YouTube studio and like look and I can see
How much my videos are liked and stuff and like versus the dislike and I know it doesn't really matter
even as long as they're hitting like or dislike I guess but
Someone comes in and or several people and
They there's just like just more dislikes than there should be and then there's like not very many of likes
So it does help out the
The algorithm I think no matter what you do, but I do appreciate
if you could give me some likes and some interaction
in the chat, so thank you.
I did a lot of cleaning today,
like I can show without fear and show,
and I know it's not perfect, but I can show I vacuumed,
I sprayed nice stuff, and do I know Victor who?
You have a number of accounts blocked from your site
Yeah, they might but it's just like I think that it's like the same person doing on multiple accounts
Just because they don't like me and it's just like
It takes away from the amount of like let's like I said if I go on tiktok
I can literally get thousands, not of people,
not of viewers, but of likes,
because you can like multiple times on TikTok.
You just tap the screen and every time you tap,
you get like a, you know, it puts up the like.
So people will literally sit there
and like, they'll sit there tapping thousands of times.
That's an amazing thought.
And then I look at this, my YouTube sometimes,
and it's like under 10 likes for like,
and like for hours long streams.
Okay, oh my, I don't know, this person's being weird.
Okay, forget them, yeah, I will.
I don't know, yeah, I got really disturbing text messages
to yesterday, it said, stay away from beta, U-N-I-G-G-E-R,
and then it was saying kind of like disturbing,
I don't know, like really uncalled for,
it's pretty evil.
know who it is too but maybe it's part of exiled one's psychological warfare
campaign that he's doing on me no but I know it's actually it's actually it's
guy named AMC and guys if you want to see what AMC looks like and what a creepy
is you can go to my discord and somebody very graciously put a video of him up
there I don't dox on my show but go to my discord you want to see what a creepy
And I know he's listening. What's up money for 20?
Seriously
It's interesting but and also Chris came came by last night and
He posted he predicted like eight
I don't know he predicted eight winners and like some sports thing he bet seven dollars and made like a hundred fifty bucks
So he's not here. Alex. He's always here. He's always here. He's obsessed with me. Absolutely obsessed
Well, I don't know. I don't know who Victor is. Oh, I don't know who that is
Victor
There's a movie called Victor Victoria I
Just don't I just don't care for that how the person's talking. I'm just gonna type them out
Go look for picture elsewhere
I don't know his photo that is
It's kind of disturbing
Exiled one. Oh my god. He's a creep too and I feel really bad because you know I talked to bronze birds sister
I talked to her before
Like months ago, right? She called in the show once.
Oh, yeah, you know, came on, she didn't come on camera.
She just called in.
She was super cool and like really nice.
And then I heard she's married to Exile
when I feel terrible for her.
I mean, I don't wanna talk, but yeah,
I won't even like, but yeah, I mean, he just sucks.
What can I say?
He sucks.
Hey Janet, how are you doing?
So yeah, I'm I know I shouldn't be a you know men's even
Bringing any hey, what's up Joker? Yeah. I
Don't know. I'm not letting these people bother me. I just I'm afraid to call them out like
You know, I just like
Yeah, but it is it is an interesting like you know
Like these storylines can take on a life of their own sometimes and it's like you can totally be painted
Completely different or things to be painted completely different than what they are and then when people start believing them. It's like, oh
It's a little bit disheartening sometimes, but
You know it's part of the heart of life and
know I get a little bit disappointed but a lot like a lot of very
relationships a lot of my friendships it's not even like I'm dating a lot of
people or you know dating anybody but it's like I feel like I've been kind of
like dumped by a lot of people and I feel kind of bad about it like
I feel like it's like kind of unceremoniously
kind of dumps, but maybe I'm doing something wrong.
Joker, yeah.
You've been bubbling the lubellas from that?
I haven't got some strange people in the chat today.
Um, oh, thank you. I look more healthy. Thank you
I'm in a better
Most for the most part a better state of mind
Yeah, and what is it people?
People are more
Likely to believe like, you know, ugly lies and the beautiful truth or something like that
Uh-oh Rhonda, why are you but why are you harassed? Oh my god
This someone's coming in harassing Trevor. Trevor come up on the panel if you want. I just want to
Get you out of the chat. I look like Steven Seagal
Steven Seagal is kind of like, isn't he kind of fat? I
Don't think
Okay, well, I'm gonna put on I'm gonna put on music video real quick just to change the energy
I'll play the play the one I opened with but I just made this one. This is really good
This call is secret door. Enjoy
Just change the energy
A marble floor of a memory we made
Trust cracked first, a small betrayal
A mirror's edge and the heart's parade
Your true, your truth and silent lies
Symbols bleeding through the veil
Tastes still like red berries, sweet but laced with hate
Hey, what if we just have to loop? There's always a crack in the cold
Don't stare straight, look sideways, a secret door glows cold
Hey, Joker, look, I can do this now.
I can do this.
Look what I can do, look what I can do.
Hold on, it's winking at you, hold on.
Don't flip it, what is Alexander McQueen saying?
Oh, he's asking for the link.
Okay, guys, come on up.
Is that easy? I don't remember there was like, I don't know.
I think it's my friend Trevor, but Trevor would usually come up on
channel. Now I've made him a mod.
Green screens are, but
I have it closer, I can make it...
I can just use the green screen
because this is like the...
And like you can make any poster you want, if it's close enough, you should be able to almost, hey, we have a guess coming up.
The day.
Alexander McQueen.
Okay, Alexander McQueen with the...
to
No, I don't know like, you know, I don't like to get privacy complaints guys. And so that's why I'm not putting up that the
comments on the screen right now
Because I got like two privacy complaints yesterday. I think easy did privacy complain
Um, and you know, it's like if you
Just let me know you can let me know either on a show or on discord or like on my message board or like there's a million ways
You don't have to like pride like I'll take I'll edit out the I'll edit out any doc saying if there's some doxing done
But you're on the I can add the same team. They're all like don't believe oh, it's not duck
Yeah, it is bro. That's like putting a picture of fucking psyche's mom up there or my mom or anyone's mom
That's not vaccine like what the fuck is that again, but it's like I mean even a picture of somebody
I mean, it's like what is it doc see if so you're walking in the pier and you're like, you know
You someone walks out past you that doc see that they're on you know, it's like it's really kind of like yeah
You're right doesn't say the name or nothing
I just I just know the person that's why you know
Swapped up and that that's part of what the beef is
Yeah, which that kind of squashed but that Trevor person coming up here with that just kind of trying to rekindle
Okay, so Ron this is Alex. Is it Alex? Oh
Alexander
McQueen is
Hey Trevor, well, I have to have you on panel to prove that it's you
Never come up. They'll never come up. They're one of those people
That was my friend Trevor the gay guy that comes. No, it's not with the blue avatar. I know you're talking about that's not
That's Trevor 84. You don't remember this person. They were here before before the travel dude
Yeah, but you thought it was the other travel so
Psychies line you don't believe that pig look look how look how they get
Definitely on moderate
I don't do panels. I don't need Docs, but you said you said you were my friend Trevor and you're live
Yeah, cuz they use that against you like in their little mind. They are your friend. Okay. I'm your friend
Yeah, cuz easy came up one day with that as you like I remember that
Yeah, doxing the his enemies and I mean like his mom. That's like him coming up with a picture of me like
And if he said I support you a lot
Yeah, I thought it was Marcy Fox once that's what don't Trevor 84 was was but uh, it's oh, it's one of them
It's they're all it's one of that bullshit
Okay, well, and I'm sorry Smith. I just I think I just
Yeah, that's all Smith's one is like we all that's all they would Smith was trying to tell you like what the fuck
Bro the toxin is easy. He got beat up. Oh
Trevor Trevor Trevor he's so funny
It's okay easy easy, but next time it before you don't before you like file
You know you I need to fill up paperwork and stuff to file that the privacy complaints
Just tell me and I'll edit that part of video out like I did you know I did anyway, but um
You know you don't have to like because that can hurt me and it's like I'm not trying I even you know
I don't know. I mean I didn't know what I was was saying was right
Um, but it's okay. I mean, you just let me know
That's weird, right? And then and that's the mom. That's not even cagada. That's the mom. Well, they're both like oh
Oh, is that satan? Okay. Hold on because there's yeah. Yeah, exactly satan
You know what and then there is like I like um
Let's try to tag rain in something and it came and I put type rain's name and then it said
Schrodinger's cat
that person's a poor bomber
Wow, I don't think it's rain though. I think it's like just using rains. They're using her name. Yeah
Yeah, and it's her actual real picture, too
That's crazy. Well, that's it's that's easy
Oh, you gotta do a screenshot the screen of anyone's picture even in the chat and you just zoom it up and make that your fucking profile
Pick and now you're that person and just change the name
Yeah
Yeah, I don't think I mean Alex was kind of like
I don't know. I mean, I can't verify any of it. I just don't know. It's like but it's like, you know
People want to be petty and complain. I don't I don't know you were saying the one mom
But you know Alex did Alice is uh, you know
Pay the price and so you know, he's uh, he's fine. Hey Apollo is all of them. You just put up a
put up a
Nice, well, I was thinking like I was thinking as like
I was like, you know what, I really, I really like Apollo and I feel bad that, you know,
I like, you know, kind of, you know, kick you off the panel, like, you know, when I
got, you know, kind of...
Got paid to
He's like I'm coming up so you can make some money and like he would like be nice enough to like you know
And he's never was you know mad about it like at all. I think never
He's like I really appreciate and I do I think you're really cool and
I don't know what that person problem with you is but I never had a problem with you
I think you're just an interesting
Good guy and so it's just interesting
Listen, I don't normally I don't like to talk about myself. Okay, but one thing about me. I
Don't pick sides
Even if you look like I stand up for what I think it's right or wrong. I
Notice that I don't
Gonna say what I mean. I don't fix eyes. I don't care
But you remember I was the first time I don't if you're better, but I say I'm not at your side
But I'm also not at your enemy
Right. I just feel bad. I was very trusting of some people and so people said, oh, this is the
This guy's following me around and stuff like that. And I was or he's trying to cause trouble and I just like I need to
Really less, you know, just like, you know, some people are
Just have their own personal beefs and stuff like that. So I
Know I know what you mean. Yeah
So yeah, I want to say one thing this implies, okay? Yeah
Please please don't when I join your panel, please don't trust my avatar only okay, and let me in because
yesterday this is
I'll listen to someone, you know, this is this
This is a select one. Okay. I
Don't know. He's an
Against you
And he, he maybe he used my me or my advertising, I mean, my avatar.
So please don't trust me.
Yeah, I've been trying to fucking tell him that forever, man.
Just once in a while, he just fucks it like forgets, you know.
But yeah, I bet it now, you know, thanks to my computer, I can, I'm getting a lot better.
I mean, I'm actually able to do a lot more with the computer, like in terms of editing
and stuff like that.
that's cool you know how to add it now like bad shit you can add up on bombs instead of erasing the whole panel
that's awesome
it can and it's also awesome I want you to add this little house to you guys want to see my little house on chicken legs
I got this on Etsy a little while ago
hmm
didn't someone pull bomb Sam in as me like shit's getting crazy
Got some chicken legs
If you heard Baba Yaga, it's a Russian witch and she has you know, she's a very ancient spirit
But you know, she's kind of some fairy tales and stuff is like this, you know
That's cool. Is that a just a decoration for
It's like a car yeah, it's like a little ghost sober decoration and I have a little bell I can ring
Okay, not a not a lol cowbell. It's just a regular cow. Okay, and uh, yeah
I won some more food. I wonder if I'm yeah, what if I won them, you know, I actually, um
Our family was his friend that I grew up with this a friend his I won't I'll say his last name was lucky and
His family won a million dollars in the McDonald's
Game in like 1985 or 86 or something like that
So actually we knew somebody that actually that won the McDonald's game
But it was a monopoly shit the monopoly game
But it was rigged most of the time though it like more recently it was rigged for like the last like
in the nineties, this kind of mafia kind of guy was the printer and he would take all the winning
the high winner game pieces and he would launder them to like his friends and like different people
like some mafia people in New York and then he he had this black lady that he like he gave one to
and she had to like go meet him like every like month with a paper bag full of like $20,000 to
And it's called McMafia, you can watch that on HBO, I think it's probably still on HBO.
It's called McMappie. Yeah, and it's all about how they rigged the McDonald's game. It was really
impossible. The guy... I think I've seen that one. It's really good. It's really good. Really
interesting, too. So the guy had all the winning game pieces, like Park Place and all that.
He was the Frencher, so he would just take them off the assembly line and put them in his pocket
and then give them back to his friends. Or his friends or like, you know, associates and stuff
burning joint, Nick is seeing that, right. And he was kind of like, and he was kind of like
You know, it kind of looks like kind of like a kind of maybe a little bit nerdy guy, but he was a gangster definitely if he was you know
Rigid monopoly game for McDonald's. He was that he was that oh
He was also kind of like an Alexander McQueen type guy where he was like kind of like I think it was a security guard, but
Alexander Mcmuffin Alexander Mcmuffin
You want to say the Alexander is not a real cop
Well, he was talking yesterday about he was in prison. I mean
Right
I don't know that many cops that spend time in prison unless they were like the correctional officers, right?
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
So you were a cop. Okay. Okay. I don't know. I'm not gonna push. I'm not gonna I'm not gonna press you on Alex
Whatever you want to be, you know, it's it's it's you it's 1999 and then ten years got out in 2019 and then you know
So for so good
But did you have like do you ever have any prison sex?
No
You're
Ten years
And you didn't wait you wasn't in prison on it
I'm excited. Are you what you weren't prison?
The part where you know this already come on man. No, I didn't seriously. I swear I swear I didn't
Well
Alex write a book or something I mean it's like that would be a you know you can go from like you're from prisoner to
To top cop, right? It's only one of our money for 20s panels the whole story
Okay
Yeah, if you go to money for 20s and go to live and it's popular
You know how you can do like the most popular shorts or live
It's the first one with the most views that one towards the end of that panel. You'll hear the whole story
Okay, the whole thing. I want to check it out
But you know thanks to Wanda, you know Wanda's
Wanda BNC Wanda BNC, but Alex you never you never even had a blowjob in in prison
Like really just you just jerked off for 10 years. I'm not gay, bro
But you were you had to jerk off so you're in a cell with another guy or you would you do it?
Alex would you do it in a shower? Do you ever have any shower sex?
No
He said oh and by the way, I was playing with my character AI because the character AI I was like
Oh Alexander McQueen sent you a message. I was like, oh my gosh, and then it you were still in the process of arresting me
Yeah, I was all spread on top of the police car. You call for backup
Backup they will came and that's got naked. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that one. It's sure
Yeah, they all started stripping. Yeah, I love character AI
and then I'm
Yeah, that's well
Your character is there's nobody before prison. I was a cop. I started robbing drug dealers. I got caught
We're gonna give me 25 to life
Cooperated with them and they gave me 10 years
Crazy
Guys, we're learning some crazy things. Yeah, Abana says
were you a fluffer?
They caught me on duty transporting kilos bro in a NYPD cop car
The how'd you get pulled over and you're in a police car because it was a set up
They were filed with the whole thing at that point. It was already set up by the feds. They they are they already had other people
In on it. They made me believe I was going to Long Island to pick up keys
Which I was but they were already in on it. It was a set up and then on the way back. They pulled me over
and
Then they said you help us or you're going to jail for 25 to life
So you help us and you can do 10 and I was like, I'll help you
Help them like help them do what like tell that. Yeah, bring down all the people
So you was basically a snitch. That's why everybody's up. You're like right snitch. Yeah, cuz of that. I'm sorry
Fucking right motherfucker 25 to life for 10 years the fuck out here. I brought down mad people. I was like, give me the pen and paper, bro
Oh Trevor, I know be careful 15 kills 15 to be exact. I've known I've known I've heard this story before but I heard
I mean, I didn't even believe it but now I believe it
No, seriously, I didn't know it
It's my first time about okay. I don't know man
Being a snitch a cop. What's next?
What's next nothing reading fucking readings with sake bro. That's what's next. Let's just forget about it and move on ten of pentacles my man ten of pentacles
Criminal couldn't you go from like
a top 90s bro, making 30 grand a year when I realized I could make 200 grand in five minutes robbing these Dominican dicks in the Bronx
So I started robbing drug dealers in the Bronx
Crime doesn't pay that's what my friends started robbing drug dealers on the job in uniform in NYPD cop cars
rolling up on them and robbing them and
We did it a lot and then eventually the feds caught on and they set me up
you know because they were already on to me so they did some
stated that I want to tell you one more on
others for the fact that
I'll tell you so you stole the drugs from me from the drug dealers and what did you do with it sell it on the street
selling
and their money I'll take your money
everything the money and the drugs
briefcases and you'd sell it to like you know like the Dominican like business man or something
Yeah, bro, there was
Low-level drug dealers which he was one or two kilos here on your grand under the bed
Go in rob them. Were you Sam and were you Sam Man's dealer? I
Don't know. Well, she was a long time ago man like 15 years ago, bro
Look at this Sam Man's dealer. Oh, oh my god
Look at that. My friends have made this video. I
Don't know if this I think this is must be the fucking stories out there for all the losers in the chat
I don't believe it. It's in the papers. It's out there man
Okay, I'm gonna look it up. That shit was in the fucking newspaper. That's why Wanda blew it up
Guys, look at this guys. Look there's look at this. There's a little puppy. Look look at this little puppy
There's a Puma look
It's fake
No
Yeah, you can't what what do you know if it's real or not, you know, how do you know?
Exactly
I see like bears and backyards like in these nice neighbors. I'm like, what the fuck's a bear doing there
Like that can't be real bro. And you know what this head part is that some a lot of people believe this shit
How stupid our people man, it's very obvious, you know use your fucking brain sir. Yes. Hello. I love Wanda
You have one I'm John one
I mean, Juanita Juanito
There we go
Hey, those look good slick back like that. You look like a seagull in his prime. You know when he was making all those fucking movies
Yeah
he was the best supposed to go
he was nothing
he was fake
all these fighting styles
he was not really a martial art
I think he was
he was a real cop in real life
I get um, I get the uncanny valley feelings when I see a like, you know, I can usually tell like
Just like something that's not right about like I don't see like looking those
They like fake people like there's a lot of fake people in the news that will have pictures of people on the news
First of all, why do they just have like one picture of somebody doesn't they have like a
Video footage of anybody. I mean, it's like there's no video footage of anybody. It's like this sa nd y h o ok guy
There's not one video of him. I mean, it's like we didn't have cameras and then you know deer 2000 to 2000
S-A-N-T-Y-S-S
H-O-K
Oh, okay
Yeah
Yeah, it was a person who did it, you mean?
Yeah, there's no video, the only video
They have one video of him playing Dan Sten's revolution from behind
And like some arcade, like it's some grainy footage
It's like, what the hell?
I mean, they would have like more video
Well, that's not big man, anyway, I forgot, who did that?
His name, oh my god, he's such a dorky looking guy
I'll show you his picture home
the
Look here here
That's a big reason why is this the end of my hook shooter
Okay, okay
That shit looks like Jim Nick will look like Jim Nick. Yeah
Jim Nick is the Sandy Hook
And then it here's the money is mugshot with like ridiculous to um his name is Adam Lanza. Let me see Adam Lanza
Okay
Look at this look at this mugshot look at that that look like a real person that looks like screech this
Six feet by the bell
Okay
The pens say that all shootings are paid
That one that one definitely was I mean that's very obvious if you look at the footage
It's just very obvious
Also, the coroner came out supposedly after doing 24 autopsies on five-year-olds, right?
And he's laughing.
I mean, it's a little bit weird, right?
He's like, he's like, he's just acting weird.
It's not like, you know, I'd be so traumatizing.
I would never even get bad at him, and he did them all himself, right?
I mean imagine I can just like this doesn't make the no survivors no survivors like really
It's just interesting. I don't know
Anyway, the medical exam
Knows that's his job though. That was a big one, right? It was like 25
224 and he was acting like he's acting like smiling and making jokes and stuff
He was making jokes. I mean, I know that sometimes corners can be a little bit morbid, but
That bad that'd be like the worst thing they've ever seen in their entire life for sure, right 24 bodies of
Just the worst
So it must be different with kids, too
I mean 24 adults is bad enough to see that but 25 kids like what's up? Yeah, I mean, yeah, right really it's like
This doesn't make sense to me and plus it's like there's never and then all the parents are like, you know
They got most of them got a free house. They're still running that charity as they end the Y hook charity and stuff
Yeah, you can tell me the guy to screw loose, right?
Also, if you can look at a lot of news stories, if you know certain codes, there are certain
codes, it's almost like puns.
You can look at some of the names and the names are like a joke.
So I swear, I can walk you through certain news stories and I'll say, look at the last
names.
you look at them and you're like, wow,
okay, this doesn't make any sense.
Like the finder's cult,
because there's something called the finder's cult, okay?
The finder's cult was supposedly like these,
okay, so the finder's cult was supposedly these,
there's all these like,
there's these two men at a playground
with like these five kids.
And they're all, all the kids were all dirty,
and like, and,
They weren't their own they weren't their kids that they were just like driving them around and stuff
And i'll tell you the names of the kids. You just tell me are these like names of like real people
okay, so um
And not to like and I don't want to like I know it's like if it would I don't if I if I believe that was true
I wouldn't be mentioning this but it's so hot in here
So obviously fake that I can say
Because okay, so the blinders fault. Here's the name of the kids. Um
Finders cult, okay
Okay, okay the names of the kids were
Let's see and now okay, okay, it says
Their names were
Okay, their names were
Okay, so it is farms, it's property, they're taking the kids to Mexico.
Where is his name?
Okay, so it's all has to do with brainwashing Satanism, right?
There are their name. Okay. I know I know one of the names by heart. Okay, so I can just say one of the names was Benjamin Franklin, okay
What yeah, yeah, it is stupid, okay
Colts I'd put Colts you LT, okay
Okay
Okay, I'm February 4th 1987
Okay, so this guy, okay, let me see.
I'll have to find the news article.
Okay.
Okay, it says CIA ties to child as the okay
It says in February 1987 an anonymous phone chip was called in to the Tallahassee police department
Reporting that six children were dirty hungry and acting like animals in the custody of two well-dressed men in Tallahassee, Florida Park
That phone call would kick off the finder's scandal a series of events and multiple investigations even more bizarre than the initial report
The trail would ultimately lead to allegations of a cult involved in ritual, A B U S E, an international child trafficking ring, evidence of child A B U S E confirmed and later denied in ties with the CIA, which was alleged to have interfered in the case.
No one was ever persecuted in the wake of the initial 1987 investigation or 1993 inquiry into the allegations of CIA involvement.
And then where are the names?
Okay, I need to find the names.
Okay, so it says, they first told the police
that they were transporting the children
to a school for brilliant children in Mexico.
However, this explanation as the purpose
of the children's trip would be changed significantly.
They probably don't have their names in here.
It's OK, it's OK, forget it.
It's just interesting, because they're so fake.
I mean, it's like, I've seen the names.
And it's just like, and there's one person named like,
her name is Mayhem.
I want to find the names, I really do.
But yeah, in any way, there's a lot of interesting cases.
That is interesting.
There's a lot of interesting. I don't say I don't say I don't believe you but
man
I know I know it's terrible. I know it's terrible
But then when you can't question things when they say certain things happen and stuff like that
But it's exactly what my story look up my story
It'll come up and then you can read it to everyone or even pull it up on the screen
Look up NYPD
For 43rd preset and I know your name, but I won't tell it
I won't say yeah, but it's gonna be a different name instead of the first name
The first name is gonna be one, but the same last name. Okay, I'll look up
Okay, New York is it New York drug smuggling. Yeah NYPD
Juan the last name. Okay. I found it. You found it. Yeah
I
Is there a mug shot in here?
There's not a mug shot there, but there is a picture somewhere. Wanda has it
Okay, I think it's scored it, but he believed was cocaine from the warehouse to the Bronx
That several times in October with someone he believed to be a high-level drug trafficker from Columbia
But he was a cooperating witness in the investigation
Blake posted that his meetings that he could provide security for the movement of drugs from Long Island to the Bronx according to the indictment
And then it says law enforcement officials put 10 brick shaped objects wrapped in brown tape in a double bag so that it appeared repackaged kilograms of cocaine.
The indictment stated at the warehouse he met another confidential witness and took the double bag from his car for the drive back to the Bronx according to the indictment.
And then it says after blank.
drop the duffel bag off the Bronx. He took a $15,000 payment from a purported Colombian drug dealer.
And then it says, I think that was the
And then they found
Look up another story though. They'll tell like a moron. I said that seriously and you're proud of this. You're a human fresh back man
Well, listen to my story
You I have your picture now
Show it Alex, can I show it?
Can I show it?
Show the whole article.
Is that you?
What?
No.
That's you?
Young Ray Liotta, baby
I don't know about me robbing the drug dealers first. That's my
point. Yeah, I see it. I see it. It says, okay, I found another. I found another case.
It's a helping drug game. It says, listen, my father used his own police car to pull up a drug related robbery.
and allegedly stole several hundred thousand dollars according to investigators the FBI
the blank uses police car to make it appear that he was taking off the cat taking off
that it's taking of the cash was a real police department seizure here comes arthur on the
exactly you listen apollo oh
hundred thousand for me away 2009 brother 2009
20 19
25 to live now, but I helped them bring down big dogs my man a lot of people went down
I gave him good meat
Guess what? I thought I got to stay low man. I will be telling you
You're from Staten Island, right? I got you brother. I
And then I got up and onus. I made it 10 years, but at least I made a lot of money, baby
You snitch on all this
Whatever, you know, you know drug dealers of big-time drug dealers. I had to bro. That was the deal
I was gonna go play life or I had to help them bring down big dogs big people like my connects basically
So they have you pictures they have your name and you're still alive you're running around
Why exactly and all your dick select came up Alex came up. Yeah, I'm trying to get me killed motherfuckers. Where are you right now, dude?
Yeah, Alex, where are you? What's your what's your current location brother?
Is that Arthur, yo, what's your current location? Yo, what's going on? What's your current location?
Don't worry about it my man
GPS it
I'm in New York City, bro
I'm telling you right now Long Island is a step away and it is much smaller than you think
I know Long Island, go back to my hand. I know from my hand to Montal
You better have eyes behind your back there Alex
Why were you one of them?
You want a person going down because those people went down for 25 to life and it's there
So I'm not even worried about them because they're fucking locked up and I don't want to die it already
I'm gonna tell you okay. Here's okay. Here's what it says about the finer thing though
It says these poor kids clearly was fake names like BB and Ben Franklin were taken into custody now
Look at the look at these pictures, okay?
Look at all screens. Oh screen. No, maybe they did look at this. Let me do you think these are real people?
I
Like no
Yeah, they were they were all found there they're all fine. Why do you gotta scream relax?
But uh, yeah
Interesting and the name is Ben Franklin and be be like be be like be like a bee
So Benjamin Franklin is the only person on a bill. That's not a president
true
He was not a president
Did you know he was a womanizer and a drunk alcoholic Benjamin Franklin
I'm just saying, he's unknown at all, but he was brilliant, but, you know, he also, he wrote a book, he wrote a whole story about farting in front of the Queen of England or something.
What?
Yeah.
Fuck.
It was all a problem.
He wrote a book about farting in front of the Queen of England or something.
Oh, no, no, no.
Skeletons and bodies buried under there
Saki now that you're doing all this research, can you look up brandon q since now you have time to look up stuff
Brandon q brandon
Basically the story I know is that this person was um on the monkey app, right?
And then so they have free shot the film on the monkey app. I don't know
The monkey app is supposedly for eight for 18 and over
the
I mean, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it up, I'll look it
Oh
Smash, you know got to do something to pass the time
Oh my god, he's Asian
Really Irish is a singer
That's him that's an Asian dude
Q U E
Brandon Q U E. Okay
It's Brandon K. Okay. No Q. No
He comes in as Brandon K because he wants people to forget or think that that's not everyone knows
he's trying to pull up on you
smart man, smart man actually
he wants to change his shit up just like easy
everybody knows about easy
easy things he's slick coming in anonymously sometimes
everybody knows about him
everybody knows he got a beat up
by fucking the
I don't
I don't see any information about it really
are you on YouTube?
the
Live streamers sigma but actually an extremely lonely jealous sexually violent instill who spends a majority of his time talking to or about
Minors were threatening to assault women arrested numerous times for assault
I was that never graduated from high school stuck in a forward square foot one bedroom moldy
Roshan Fessett apartment and slowly bloating from a combination of meth stress guilt shame and alcohol
Um, I don't have permission to play this person's channel. I mean, I don't know if they'd have to
Do come on bro. That you're
No, it just seems like I don't I don't know there's I can show the picture
It says nothing to see here guys literally nothing at all
I said
So what the hell did he do besides be a bomb man?
Like stop tiptoeing the line psyche. I just I can't play the video because it's like somebody else's video and
Anything on YouTube that's on you
And it says look it's pregnant Beyonce does she look pregnant what it looks like some kind of what is this?
You can play content
Is this what he looks like right here?
I was doing society
Looks like everyone's teeth up here. Actually, I'm noticing everyone on the paddles missing
Somebody I'm like, oh my god, I'm gonna fuck with this little tooth too. What the fuck now you are so yeah, I never seen you but
a lot of motherfuckers will be
the best life I guess, huh?
That's life!
Gotta take care of your teeth.
You know I once said the dentist ones and there was a post on the one that said
you don't have to floss all your teeth, just the one you want to keep.
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
I'm just going to play a new commentary on it. Let me see other
Alexander do that. Alexander does that. So what's wrong with it? She could do it. Everybody could do it, right?
Alexander. Yes. Where is she? She'll do it in a second. Get over here
30-minute break right now. It's so weird. Ryan, mommy alerts snorted coke versus Brandon
Sandra does PowerPoint presentations about people
with graphs and shit
and
I'm going to try to
tell you ran into controller
and
never I heard the name all the time and lately I've seen what it is it's just like fat lady
like I don't know
you guys are from Long Island though
and she's from here
and here we go here we go ladies and gentlemen
here we go
Oh my goodness, here we go.
WineMommy views!
We have a new commentary.
Yeah, you have to speak over it.
Hello ladies and gentlemen, and welcome to IP2 WineMommy Alert,
where we discuss all the latest gossip and drama from your favorite streamers.
I am your hostess Debra, and let's get right into the tea.
Nice to meet you Debra.
I am officially back, doing the news on this show.
It has been so long since I brought the gossip to the table.
Yes.
I hope you enjoy this show.
Sit back, make yourselves comfortable, and grab yourself a wine.
For our first story stream, Sniper named Swimmer picked Sniper to Ice Poseidon.
I don't know who Swimmer Nick is.
He must be one of those sex tourist streamers, like Slightly Homeless, or Kang Joel.
I don't watch the travel streamers, because they are so boring and I much prefer Gucci's shouting on an RV.
I don't think that's good.
It's just gonna be mad for us tonight after I leave.
Oh, no.
I don't watch the travel streamers, because they are so boring and I much prefer Gucci's shouting on an RV.
I think you get the wrong video, brother.
I want to see what you're doing for the rest of the night after I leave.
I bet after I leave your shit's just going to be massively boring.
You're not going to eat any food.
What was your stream like?
My stream was amazing.
Can we skip?
Really?
Yeah.
And how many views?
A 100 man.
I did a memorial for Vaxxon's exercise.
That brought the roof down man.
Thank you.
See that chat how it moves man?
Damn.
That's a lot. I don't like I don't like I don't like this kind of three masses. This is not
Lawson's and troubles. We must like you need a bottle. I don't like it. You know, it's like
You know
I'm gonna be honest. I'm not even in high school yet. I drink like this. I'm going to die
When I mean oh my god
When I was in 8th grade, trust me, I was bringing shit to school.
No, I hate when people tell me I'm an alcoholic.
Take a shot.
That's junior high school, bro.
There's a little kid.
He's talking about it.
That's child! That's child! That's child! That's child! That's child!
No, I'm not recording you bro. I'm not recording you. I'm not recording you. I didn't record you bro
That's just your casual day today and I got a girlfriend, bro
What is this anyone has bigger tits than the well Katrina
William went bro you live with your fucking daddy
All right psyche I would love to know your comments after knowing he was speaking to minors
knowingly why she didn't jail
Very inappropriate you talking sexually. I think that I think on YouTube like the rule is
like
You can talk to I mean, I you can talk to people
That maybe I don't know but it's not in a sexual way. I guess it's very inappropriate, right? It's like but uh
What are your comments to it fs YouTube's rules f all that what what more out of the morals
What do you say? It seems like he was I mean he was live streaming it
It's like it doesn't look like he was like necessarily even
Pretend you're not a new to know you're at a restaurant with Arthur privately. What are you?
Imagine a girl comes on your panel, okay, and she says she's on my head what
Well, it's like, you know, just like, oh, like, no talking, like, you know, like, especially that way, you know, it's not appropriate, of course.
It's not appropriate.
I said you see now, I think when you guys call L.D. a pedo
I think you have videos of him like this, but you know, right? There's no L.D. shit with like little girls like this
See I'm interested on our own size opinion. If you're an age girl and she admits he's an age
What would you do if you join your penis?
You fucking leave, bro. You say
love up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up up
immediately exit not like you know be seeing your talk it or stuff right that's definitely pretty disgusting but psyche so you're telling me you would
speak to the lady you would speak to the girl but cuz it's okay but as long as
you're not talking sexually I say anything like that I said if as soon as the
person had a you know or it's like you know even if they appeared you know so
No, I said no, I said immediately stop in here. It's definitely not
But if the monkey app is supposed to be for 18 or over and so I bet once you get to that point where she identified herself
It's like eighth grade or whatever the question is once you set up 15. What would you have done?
What would you set to what would you say?
So now if Brandon Q tries to join here again, what would you do?
Would you I don't want to talk to him. I don't have anything to say to him. I don't know him. I just
But it's like these are kind of like
Yeah
It's like this is good. This is good because like that's like letting I'll be
Don't get all crazy
Because you're not specifically saying
an app that's supposed to be for 18 or over and then there's somebody breaking the rules of the app and on there
then
That's it's getting in the murky area, but once they identify themselves obviously
You know, and you don't you don't engage in sexual conversation
But you know, there's a transgender person that her name is Sabrina tw and she goes
And she has people in her chat right and just you know, she's in the chat not in the not on video or anything and so
and she goes oh if you're um
She's like, oh, you're 13. Well, you have to have your parents from it or you're under 13
You have your parents permission to be here. You're over it. I mean, it's like and so I think you're
As long as it's not a sexual I don't know a sexual way
Your life chicken little kitchen I'll be interacting with adults online
Because it's like, okay
I know why do you want to go down to like you two rules? Why can it be your rule where I don't want miners in here period?
Devils advocate and say okay, let's go to legalistic things. Okay, it's like right and so
It's not like you're meeting somebody in person and having any
What it's about what I'm saying is like it's like what I don't know you know the phone somebody you call somebody
It's like you're talking to somebody on the phone
Situation that we're in clearly Brandon Q was being sexual knowing
My hypotheticals, okay now you're talking about we're doing hypotheticals. We're if we have a whole situation
We have a real-life scenario. We don't have to do hypotheticals
Okay, I said it was very inappropriate and he should not have been doing that
the
So so is a 17 year old person allowed in a YouTube chat are they allowed to be 17 is a lot different than for 13 man
But in the 13 17 year old are they allowed in YouTube chats or are they banned from YouTube chat?
That's what I want to know. You know on tiktok you can be 13 and be on tiktok, right?
Don't know if there's rules for that, but in New York, you can't touch anyone under 18
Are you gonna jump for a long time my friend if you touch a girl under 18?
I wouldn't want to be with a 17 year old online if so 17 year old came up here in our advance like that's that's a kid to me
Like Noel is where I draw the line how old is she like 23 like that
Well, it's 30 years old. Okay. And so you can say mentally certain age. I know she's like 24 or so I'm 23 20
She's very young. So she's not 30. No, I was 23
Yeah
Yeah, I didn't know his background or anything about it, but again, it's like, okay, so I've seen that that was definitely
No proof of something
what now so L
Okay, what we're talking about another person with a seven no no question is Brendan Q. Is he still allowed here?
Um, I have no reason to have what he's still allowed that guy's been here
Today in the morning. He was here last night. I don't know the story. I didn't know the story
Um
What? I want to know. I want to know about UNZ, the groomer.
What about me and him?
Are you friends?
Uh, no.
We're not friends. Why now did you let that guy open the panel side? Well, you haven't seen this
All right. Yeah. Yeah, exactly. You didn't know
You didn't know correct when you let him up again if he comes back now
You know when you have panels like hey, are you allowed to talk to Charles Manson and do an interview with him over?
It's like you can interview people certainly right? I don't know. It's like am I
I'm not going to have a minor on the panel talking to them, obviously, right?
I don't know.
It's like, um, it's just, it's a question of like, oh, it's a really, really
anguish thing.
I'd be willing to talk to almost anybody because it's over.
It's not in person and stuff like that.
And it's not involving anything.
It's just because this person, I don't know.
I would like to ask him about that.
Maybe I'd ask him more in detail now that I know more information about it.
But, oh, so.
You know, is he why isn't he in prison if it's illegal, right? I mean, it's like I don't understand
Why is he walking free if it's like he did is you know or anybody if someone's 17
uh, in 364 days
I'm saying I'm saying if you talk to somebody and what if you don't I mean there's certain things
He's not in prison because technically he didn't touch the girl like in real life. I don't think
That's a loophole man. He should be in prison the prick
You think they fixed the legal right now?
Man, this is one thousand is weird.
Thank you.
Go get a shot.
Say, go get the Bruce keys.
Let me see this in general, okay?
Besides of the laws, if you are a parent, you know,
like myself, you see things different, you know?
If you are a parent yourself, I don't know.
My my children if she gets the mistake and go to practice right? Yeah exactly something's wrong with the parents in that situation
Like your kids should not be online with the old man
Change the laws make it easy go to
Ever ever good
How about like, you know, you know, there are
Parents and how about the so so the parents the parent has spread so, you know, it's like
are people allowed, what about, what about teachers?
Are they allowed to talk about, I don't understand.
Like, if it's a sexual, right?
Oh, well, a little bit of teachers.
Right, so you know what we're gonna do eventually
is gonna have all AI teaching the kids
and so they don't have to interact with adults anymore.
That's a great idea, man, actually.
Yeah, I agree.
It raised a pervert teacher out of the equation.
I like it.
By the way, yeah, that was a scrap metal person.
Social acceptance in laws are okay. So social acceptance in laws are but you know laws are
Don't just grab metal person. Oh my god. Yeah, he was looking for a real view is he was looking for alex's grill
He said alex's grill my grill. Hey, do you want to hear this person on the phone right here?
There's motherfucker on the phone. Oh shit. Oh my god
This is your band get out of here get out of here. What do you do?
And Arthur, you're about to go too because I don't like you like trying to put a jacket on me because I'm not
I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I'll leave the pen, I
Don't have anybody it's like what does it have to do with me really even if I have that person on brandon quick quayer
Okay, what if I want to ask you about it? What if I want to ask about it?
What if I would have given like what were you thinking? What was going through your mind?
Yeah, and they're gonna execute you just for talking to the guy. We have yeah
It's crazy
Hello
No
Alexander's grill what dicks you know what he so pissed the Tony cuz I went at him and I was like you're gonna go to jail
I'm gonna fuck with this investigation. He was like, oh, yeah, Alex. We'll see
And then now he's like doubling down what an asshole
You know what? It's like it turns into this whole like
witch hunt of like oh my like like with you know
LD is very controversial, right? But he was and now it's like it seems like it's not controversial anymore
I don't know. It's like what about yeah, so
Yeah, see now D like all these people are like viewed the same way, right?
There's like a little group of them that they think do this shit
I'm assuming that's me.
Someone came on there and they were like, oh, Sandman,
it plays Roblox.
So he's this, no, and they're good.
They're communicating with minors.
Have you played with some of these games and stuff
like that online?
Is that I don't understand it's like you're not even seeing the person but it's like, you know
There's just chat rooms. I don't know. I don't on these games, but I don't play
Oh, wow
Is that why they call him that because he plays an online game with little kids?
But it's just a game like he's just gaming it up. You see oh, he was like selling you Geo cards and stuff like that
Oh God, so they're calling that's so funny
And but they're saying oh he plays roblox so this and I was like no if you play a roblox
that doesn't mean anything like a lot of kids games don't like what the hell's a man doing
I don't know but you know what there's some computer games that are like you know all
the sometimes parents like to say I don't know I think parents just basically should run should
run the laws and stuff for that you know it's like I don't I'm just gonna stay out of it and
just deal with adults you know I so I don't know it's it's like uh people just try to put
Sam ends the ball it's like so I don't I don't necessarily
agree with like putting jackets on people for like all sorts of things, but in this bread-and-quays situation
Yeah, he seems like you know douchebag and he should not have been like talk it once that girl said it was in eighth grade
It's obviously further computer out the window. He's sitting there on his stream on live not not thinking anything was wrong. So I
Don't know he was streaming on himself doing it. It is messy, right?
So there's no proof who is much smelly
Stop the link. Okay, look he home
Yeah, let's get low key up here just low key. I think has no sense
We're we can have a calm conversation. Okay, hold on a second
And by the way, I don't think say I don't think salmon is part like
Oh, but you know what?
Do you see how Arthur left once I brought up Zeya?
That's pretty interesting.
Do you like when I do that to you, Arthur?
Do you like when I start making insinuations?
No, you don't.
And so I'm just doing what you did to me, right?
You can't type it that so many words ban.
We'll just don't say the ban words
for the prediction of the chat.
And where towers are just lame.
Lame is, I have the letter N.
Six stage
Can someone ban six stage seven stage eight stage ninth stage and 10th stage, please
Okay, hold on a second. Can you be just be just ban anybody with the word sage in our name?
Please let's get it. You don't really have to I mean it means fine. I mean people get passionate about this stuff, but
I think people go cuckoo for Cocoa Pups in a certain way.
It goes a little bit far with like everybody's
accuses of all this stuff.
And yeah, it goes a little crazy.
I'm just gonna make sure there's the real low key
while I'm on the tip there.
Um, here we go.
I think it's a good conversation to have too.
I did something like saying, people saying,
oh, oh, oh, they left, they left, oh.
Why'd you live never comes up in those
Carols hey careless Kate. I I was just kidding. I say just fine. I didn't I didn't brand anybody. Oh ghost is here
I did I dropped the link goes
Hold on. It's right here. Goat's tobo
Oh
Shut up six days. Yeah, just ban that person that's saying that. Okay. She's a bad signal. Okay. It wasn't her. It was seen abana
Why don't don't go to bat so fast. Yeah, it wasn't her
She asked for the link, but they came up. I'm too fast. Thank you. Look, it's the Alexander McQueen guy even own Alexander McQueen one
Now I have the grooming cult
Trying to pour them on my my uh
My show then at somebody ban. Um, get up here ghosty. Tell me I'm a beautiful man. Get ghosty up here
What's the compliment us?
Yes, uncle
Is that weed or a tobacco that is tobacco at the tiny little bit
Nice
Shut up. I can ban who I want. It's my check. It's my chat and I'll ban up my work, too
You can ban who I want, if you add your own show, hitch you can kick
The grooming cult, who is that? I don't know. I think it's
I don't know. I don't want to say anything about the grooming cult. Yeah, um, you know who it is
Grooming coach. So that's what they mean by that these kind of dudes that groom little girls online like I'm trying to figure it all out with the
Talk I hear
Alexandra Bayer she covers the extensive
You can go look at her old streams nice
She knows she's more familiar with the extensive files on these assholes basically
basically, you know
I'm gonna stay away from them. Okay. Yeah, exactly. I'm not a good topic. I'm I don't like it. Thanks. How are you chicken cakes?
Hey, go see
Hey ghost, how about the ghost song guys, how about the ghost song? Go soon
Go song go song
Where is it? This one?
It's a strange transmission.
Where is it? I don't know. I need to...
I'm looking closer. Okay.
Oh, here it is. I see it.
The ghost song.
Enjoy, guys.
We made this yesterday.
Permission to crash out
Ghost already did it
That's how you know, the haunts are live
Lights flicker, chats in the ride
And somewhere goes about to die
Heroes are loud like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts
I was reborn
May I have permission to crash out?
Coastal ready did it took the whole crowd
Heart of gold voice of fire
That's good work, may I have permission to crash out?
The stakes get higher
Dumb dumb that's his war
Psych is proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
I got a pair of sneakers from McQueen, $3,000. All I wear is McQueen. Dexiel.
a dream dumb dumb to the ones who doubt he's the reason the flame never went out so raise your
glass the ghost are out it's ghost baby it's a ball
Ghosts for all you've done for the show. Thank you so much. Love ghosts
Ghosts is actually I don't want to I don't want to spoil it, but he's actually
He's actually nicer than he might think
He's actually good
No, he just likes to he likes to debate and he likes to have permission to crash out. You like that one. Okay, I
Love it. Hey, it's age. You want to threaten me boy?
You don't you don't threaten
Excel one Excel two Excel three you just keep kicking
Tony Tony's asking me to Tony's messaging me. Fuck you Tony. Go fuck yourself
I'm before I before I tell everyone to go to my discord and look at your stupid dumb
You got a video of him. Yes on my disc
Let me just score. I'm about to play it and I'm going to delete this stream. I'm going to show you this ugly ass.
I'm going to show you.
This fucking asshole thinks he can't get touched. Play it. Let's see the middle boy.
You want to see it? Everyone's going to see him. Everyone's going to see what a dumbass this guy looks like.
Okay, here we go.
Yup.
It's worth it.
Okay, here we go.
He's Benjamin. He's Benjamin Kowalski.
He called me an N word in my chat, so.
Okay, anyway.
Okay, got it. Got it.
Want to see this fool here you go guys
Here you go, let's see
Oh, he's always typing that and we're gonna be back. He's he fat. He's he's disgusting
Okay, guys, but this is gonna be a present. I mean, it doesn't mean any of this dream, but I'm okay here we go
,
Oh, wow
Keep making threats Tony keep making threats the police see all this
That's gonna be on Twitter tic-tac Instagram
Guys everyone everyone share this everyone can share it anywhere they want, you know
He's gonna be like, yeah, anyone can share this video. This is a public video. He made himself. Okay. Oh
My god, who sent it to you who's the
Prince
Now you bring that to the police and say this is the air so
We know who you are
Mr. BK. Oh, you're striking my discord? Oh, no! Not my discord!
You can't strike shit.
I'm gonna strike you, strike you. What a pussy.
You're a bitch. You're gonna post a video of, hold on.
You called my family, you send yourself doorknocks.
Okay, I'll play a video of Juicy.
I'm gonna post a video, so you're spending a P-E-D-O-S.
Okay, okay.
It sounds like a two year old's fucking going crazy.
He's so retarded, he's so retarded.
Okay, anyway, so let's see.
I will just post my I'm still very connected in the NYPD, my man. All right there Baloney
Go ahead. Go ahead family in the NYPD made you should. Oh, I am in one
Now he's saying that he's text messaging me that he loves
PDFs
Of course it does
They sexy me
Well, you shouldn't be you know, you shouldn't you shouldn't okay. Let's see. Here's my discord anyone wants to go see the photo
and by everybody you put it in the back I don't want to go to discord but I'll see it eventually so
Okay, it's great
And you'll see the name first now you got to pick this guy looks like and by the way you are now on
The police watch list by the way, okay, not just now but always, okay, let's see
He's punching air right now. He's biting. Oh, I should see the messages. You should see the message. Oh my god
Can I show the message I can show the messages?
I'm gonna post this this link though for you guys
Join my discord and I'm gonna have to I'm gonna have to just to go see this and then I'll just enjoy but
He's freaking out
I'm not gonna say his name. I'm not gonna say his name or anything. Here we go. Who did it? I'll say it. It's Benjamin
Okay, but don't say it's awesome. We'll do the last one
Here's the discord link. There you go
You can see you can see the whole thing. Whoa, the link is dropped. I see it, baby
Oh shit Benjamin one two coming for you three four better lock your door
No, he's mad. Oh, I was you got a mad house. You know, you know, five six
He's space he wasn't expecting that right, you know, he's the one that you're saying that I'm cool
He likes to do it when you're live. So, you know, it makes him feel cool
What I think
He said I'm harassing
Him when he's saying, oh my gosh, I can read the messages. You're harassing him
Here's what he says
I would just stop contact right now with him
And I GGR strike your discord you bitch you're threatening me threatening me you called my family you send yourself doorknocks
Okay, I'm gonna put you up you defending PDFs and manure. I'm gonna honk my horn
Strike and then he puts me in Manson's vagina stop begging me for manure I'm Ben sage now on BNM Connie
Check me my man. You got them
These are these are public these are publics my friend. Oh my god, I should
You gotta go this dream will be deleted. Okay. Bye guys. I'll eat back later